(Q11（单选）) ⭐ welcome back/again —— 再次欢迎
⭐ councillor —— 议员；地方政府委员｜city council —— 市议会
⭐ tell sb about sth —— 告诉某人关于某事｜fast-growing —— 快速发展的｜suburb —— 郊区
⭐ welcome to the show —— 欢迎来到节目
⭐ community consultation —— 社区咨询｜there has been... —— 已经有……
⭐ try to do sth —— 努力做某事｜address concerns —— 解决担忧/问题｜local groups —— 当地团体
⭐ hear from sb —— 收到某人的意见/消息｜be worried about —— 担心｜in particular —— 尤其｜increasing speed —— 不断增加的速度
[Q11答案句] ⭐ only a matter of time —— 只是时间问题｜before sth happens —— 在某事发生之前
(Q12) ⭐ do something about sth —— 采取措施解决某事｜area of concern —— 关注的问题｜overhead power lines —— 高架电线
⭐ ask if something could be done —— 询问是否可以采取措施｜old —— 老旧的
[Q12答案句] ⭐ be happy to report that... —— 很高兴宣布……｜agree to do sth —— 同意做某事｜move sth underground —— 将某物移到地下｜at a cost of... —— 花费……
⭐ improve the look of... —— 改善……的外观｜as well as —— 以及；同时
(Q13) ⭐ good to know —— 很高兴知道｜mean an increase in... —— 意味着……增加｜local businesses —— 当地企业
[Q13答案句] ⭐ bear the cost —— 承担费用｜themselves —— 他们自己
[Q13干扰项⭕️] ⭐ extra funds —— 额外资金｜put funds into sth —— 将资金投入某事｜tree planting —— 植树
(Q14（地图）) ⭐ put together —— 制作；整理｜send out —— 分发；发送｜resident —— 居民
⭐ mark sth on a map —— 在地图上标出某物｜proposed changes —— 计划中的变化
⭐ mature pine trees —— 成熟的松树｜provide shelter and shade —— 提供遮挡和阴凉｜just to the right of —— 就在……右侧
(Q15) ⭐ in order to —— 为了｜address problems —— 解决问题｜pavement —— 人行道｜widen —— 拓宽
⭐ reduce the speed of... —— 降低……速度｜vehicle —— 车辆
(Q16) ⭐ separate A from B —— 将A与B分开｜residential street —— 住宅街道｜main road —— 主干道
⭐ entry of... —— ……入口｜be painted red —— 被涂成红色
⭐ mark clearly —— 清晰标记｜act as a signal —— 起到信号作用｜slow down —— 减速
(Q17) ⭐ make sure that... —— 确保……｜pedestrian —— 行人｜signage —— 标识｜intersection —— 十字路口
⭐ erect a sign —— 设置标志｜junction —— 交叉口｜enable sb to do sth —— 使某人能够做某事｜at all times —— 始终
(Q18) ⭐ control the flow of traffic —— 控制交通流量｜install traffic lights —— 安装交通灯｜half way down —— 中途；中段｜where it crosses... —— 与……交叉的地方
(Q19) ⭐ not only... but also... —— 不仅……而且……
⭐ get sb to do sth —— 让某人做某事｜research —— 研究｜incorporate A into B —— 将A融入B｜on the other side of... —— 在……另一侧
(Q20) ⭐ agree to do sth —— 同意做某事｜children's playground —— 儿童游乐场｜at the other end of... —— 在……另一端｜close to —— 靠近
⭐ next stage —— 下一阶段